

# **UX/UI** Designer

fredkim.design fredk@usc.edu 714.975.1607

### **SKILLS**

| Design           | Research             | Tools       | Languages  |
|------------------|----------------------|-------------|------------|
| Wireframing      | Usability Testing    | Sketch      | HTML5      |
| Prototyping      | User Surveys         | InVision    | CSS3       |
| Logo Design      | Competitive Analysis | Illustrator | Javascript |
| Content Strategy | Storyboarding        | Photoshop   | jQuery     |

## **PROJECTS**

### Skylake - Cloud Sharing app

Skylake is a cloud redesigned for a faster, cleaner, and more intimate collaboration experience. It directly addresses the competition's four biggest problems - tedious navigation, ambiguous UI, feature bloat, and cluttered workspace. The solution comprises of minimal UI, one-click navigation, organized architecture, and global accessibility of features.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Bloc - UX/UI Design Apprentice | Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

- •. Implemented user-centric & process-driven design from ideation to testing.
- Empathized user needs via surveys, personas, stories, flow charts, & test feedback.
- Tested and iterate through Lo-Fi/Hi-Fi prototypes with InVision, Sketch, & Illustrator.
- Built cross-platform and responsive interfaces with HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript.
- Created brand identity with logo design, type selection, & style guides.

### **Booz Allen Hamilton** - Strategy Consultant Feb 2016 - Jun 2018

- Created system plans & technical requirements for \$10 million missile range projects.
- Analyzed schedule & resource conflicts across 20+ Satellite Communication programs.
- Supported GPS proposal by aligning candidates to work statements and drafting resumes.
- Curated career development guides and training courses for 250+ staff to bolster growth.

### Siemens PLM Software - System Engineer Intern | Jan 2015 - Jul 2015

- Resolved 100+ client tickets by diagnosing CAD configurations and determining root cause.
- Provided post-sale product and operating system support to high profile customers.

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of Southern California** - B.S. in Mechanical Engineering 2011 - 2015

Design for User Experience, Computational Solutions to Engineering Problems

**Certifications:** ICAgile Certified Professional, Certified SolidWorks Associate